Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/nguyen-duy-binh-98a38b188 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

C#

Angular

JavaScript

Nguyen Duy Binh

Senior Software Engineer at Corsair Vietnam

Summary

I am a full-time developer with over 6 years of experience in the C++ language. Leveraging my skills, experience, and deep understanding of programming, I aim to contribute as a professional employee and bring significant value to the company.

Experience

Corsair

Senior Software Engineer October 2022 - Present (2 years 7 months)

Develop new features, fix bugs, and integrate new gaming devices into the iCUE software to control lighting effects, key assignments, configuration settings, key actuation, and other functionalities using C++ and the Qt framework (QML)

FUNIX University
Student Mentor
July 2020 - Present (4 years 10 months)
Vietnam

SecureAge Technology Senior Software Engineer October 2020 - October 2022 (2 years 1 month) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Develop a completely new front-end and back-end for a Security and Antivirus application using C++ and the Qt framework(QWidget).

Huyndai Mobis Software Engineer July 2019 - October 2020 (1 year 4 months) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Develop three tools for controlling sensor systems (LIDAR, RADAR, CAMERA, SVM, etc.), recording sensor data, and rendering multiple

data types for automotive applications using the Qt framework in Linux and Windows OS:

- Logger Tool: Using Qt framework, develop server software utilizing shell scripts to remotely connect client software (in a car) with multiple devices such as cameras, LIDAR sensors, GPS, etc., to record data.
- Render Tool: Using Qt and the Point Cloud Library (PCL), develop software for Windows OS to render images, map positions, and LIDAR 3D point clouds.
- Annotation Tool: Using Python, the Vispy library, and PyQt5, render LIDAR point cloud data, identify objects, draw 3D cuboids, and export metadata for training models. Develop new features, optimize, and upgrade performance for LIDAR curation and 3D annotation tools using Vispy, Python, PyQt5, and Open3D.
- Create a new labeling function with a Brush in 3D point cloud view using Python and the Qt framework..

VietUnion Online Services Corporation (Payoo) Software Engineer January 2019 - June 2019 (6 months) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

- Developed a new POS machine and released 4 high-performance versions with more features and less handling (using C/C++ languages).
- Developed a new Paytouch POS software in 2 months after self-teaching C#, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, and Angular framework

FPT Software
Software Engineer
December 2017 - January 2019 (1 year 2 months)
District 9, Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Participated in large projects involving ultrasound machines. Analyzed ultrasound images and videos, and created charts after analysis. Developed three new measurements for ultrasound machines. Handled gestures (tap, double tap, rotate, zoom, etc.) on touchpads and trackpads to draw measurements. Developed custom controls for setting machines using MFC

Education

APTECH Computer Education

Higher Diploma in Software Engineering · (2015 - 2018)

FPT University
Bachelor's degree, Computer Science